Uh, come with me,
I'll walk you to the apartment.
(Beverley:)Oh, all right. Would you like
to exchange pleasantries on the way?
- Yeah, sure, I guess.
- All right, you start.
(Penny:)I've always been curious.
What was Leonard like when he was little?
BEVERLY: Oh, I think you mean young.
He's always been little.
(Howard:)Right.
What was he like when he was young?
(Beverley:)You'll have to be more specific.
(Penny:)Oh, um, okay, like five or six.
(Penny:)- Five.
- Oh, well, at that age...
...he was in what Freud would call the
phallic stage of psychosexual development.
(Beverley:)An outmoded theory, of course.
(Beverley:)But the boy did spend most of his waking
hours with a tight grasp on his penis.
Oh, yeah, Leonard mentioned
you were a psychiatrist.
(Beverley:)Well, that is one of my degrees.
My primary field is neuroscience.
(Penny:)Oh. Well, I'm an actress.
[GIGGLES]
(Beverley:)Why?